God dammit…
Freakin' pisses me off.
Where'd that damn thing go?
Anjuro Katagiri, a.k.a. Angelo.
Known as the sickest, most heinous
criminal in Japanese history
He continually murdered
from the age of twelve,
his final homicide being…
Milkman! Watch where you step!
…viler than
the foulest dog shit.
In March, 1994,
he came across three
fourteen-year-old boys,
two of which he proceeded
to rape and murder.
Step in something?
Suppose I did.
Freakin' pisses me off!
Someone's letting their dog shit
in front of my house…
I think I might just keep it
to dump in the owner's
pocket tomorrow morning.
Um… I left your milk over there.
Until next time.
Hey…
I don't recognize you.
Yeah, I'm just a temp for today.
Huh…
The third boy came from
a rich family,
so Angelo demanded ransom.
That's what led to his arrest.
Hate to nitpick,
but the seal's broken.
Huh?
Is that so?
Look for yourself, here!
You don't say…
It's broken, see?
Yeah. Sorry about that.
Well, so long!
Thanks.
Welcome.
Damn bitch!
Sharp-eyed little vixen.
If only that shrew and punk
Josuke had drunk the milk,
my Stand, Aqua Necklace,
would've already
overpowered them!
More?
You are a good
little shitter, aren't you?
When the police raided
Angelo's torture den,
they found a horrific sight.
The boy lay murdered,
his genitalia
severed and nailed to
the pillar that stood nearby
Worthless bastard…
Can't pick up your own dog's shit, huh?
Had to toss your dirty cig
on the ground, huh?
Well you got whatcha deserved,
smug bastard!
You wanna be a
goddamn pompous ass?
Then you'll swallow my Stand
and die like the dirty rat you are!
JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
These faceless gazes pass by one another
A wound to the heart changes our everyday
Encounters without boundaries
The bizarre is our normal U-yeh
These ordinary mornings,
we're laughing on the surface
Mysteries drawn to each other,
identity still unknown
Without a heads up,
it's quietly lurking somewhere in this town
Although we bicker and complain
In the end, we celebrate
Dancing through the everyday
Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town
EPISODE 2
JOSUKE HIGASHIKATA! MEETS ANGELO
Well, it looked like the Stand
took over the robber's body…
I mean, he jumped into his body.
He didn't attack me.
Was Angelo nearby?
You know, the guy in the picture.
Nope, didn't see him.
Dammit,
my hair looks like shit today
Listen.
His Stand's weak, but he can
control him from afar.
It somehow infiltrates
people's bodies.
I'll be at your house soon.
Huh? Soon?
Don't eat or drink anything
till I get there.
That includes tap water.
And stay away from the shower
and bathroom. Got it?
Hold on a sec.
I still haven't told
my mom you're here.
She's usually pretty tough,
but he still makes her cry.
I think she still loves Mr. Joestar.
One look at you, and she'll know
exactly who you are.
Josuke, where'd you get
this picture?
It's the milkman
from this morning…
You know him?
Josuke! What's wrong?
Crap! I'm too late!
It was hiding in my mom's coffee,
now it's in her mouth!
Hello? Josuke? Hey! Josuke!
Josuke, want some coffee?
Sure, why not?
Milk and sugar, too?
Milk and sugar it is.
Josuke? Milk and sugar, right?
Yeah.
Hello? Mr. Jotaro?
I got him, but…
What?
What do I do with him?
How in the hell…
Careful.
Angelo's likely spying
on your house as we speak.
Keep your eyes glued
to that Stand.
I'll be right there.
Angelo survived his execution
and broke out of prison
only because he had use
of a Stand
Exactly what he can do,
I still don't know
Dead ball!
Sayonara!
Dead ball, game over, sayonara!
That's a good boy.
You little shit!
Josuke!
– I'll murder them both!
– Get a move on or you'll be late!
That little pissant and
his smoking hot mom!
I've got to get that damn cap off…
Or break the bottle…
Is that…
– Higashikata…
– Home.
– I know that name.
– I'm too old for this night shift crap.
So this is
Officer Higashikata's house.
Last we met, I was twelve.
Those were the good ol' days!
I know everything there is to
know about you.
Everything, fucker!
Freeze.
Josuke, what happened to
going to class?
Grandpa! They let you
take your gun home now?
Stuff it, smart ass! Answer me!
I-I'm going!
I'm just waiting for someone.
You goober!
You're looking at a toy gun!
I really gotcha good.
Guess that means the first win
this week goes to me!
Fine, fine. You win.
What's the matter?
Not gonna even argue with me?
I'm fine. And mom already left.
Shouldn't you be in bed?
You must be tired.
Now, for our next story
The death count in a bizarre
chain of grisly incidents
involving severe internal trauma
to the victims' eyes and ears
has risen this morning to
a staggering seven.
While the incident appears to be
isolated to the town of Morioh,
police are now working to
determine whether the trauma
can be tied to disease
or aggressive behavior.
This isn't the first
I've heard of this.
If you ask me,
this is no accident.
Something wicked is
lurking in this town.
I can feel it.
Grandpa…
He's here…
I know all your quirks, Higashikata.
Nothing like a nice brandy
after a long night's work, right?
Josuke, grab the bottle and get in.
We'll take it where
no one can get hurt.
Good idea.
G-Grandpa…
Josuke Higashikata!
You've really messed up now!
You looked away,
and now you're shit outta luck!
You got too cocky,
you little prick!
I have to say it's invigorating
bringing a pretentious bastard crashing
down to earth in a puddle of despair!
Close! Impressive…
Still think you're hot shit, eh?
You're a dead man!
Hear that? Your life is over!
Grandpa opened the bottle.
Don't worry, I've got this.
It just looks bad.
My Stand can easily…
All better.
No, there's no way he's…
He'll open his eyes any second.
My Stand heals people.
I've done it a million times.
I fixed my friends' broken bones…
Grandpa! Hey!
Quit messing around!
Don't tell me you've
passed out from last night's shift?
Come on, enough with
all the stupid games!
Grandpa! Grandpa!
Josuke…
I've healed him…
It's said the human organism
must destroy in order to survive.
Your power is an unparalleled act
of compassion
in an otherwise brutal world.
But no amount of love,
can bring back a life lost.
No Stand
can break death's grip.
For thirty-five years,
he never stopped looking
after this town.
He could tell
danger was lurking…
And when he heard
news breaking of
Angelo's return to murder,
I saw a man of honor,
ready to protect his people.
Angelo has left many victims
in his wake.
It's safe to say
many other victims
from Morioh lie waiting
to be uncovered.
His murders are without motive.
He kills for the thrill of killing.
And he'll keep murdering.
After he kills you and your mother.
I'll…
I'll take the baton.
I'll protect mom and this town.
Nothing will stop me.
AQUA NECKLACE
ANJURO KATAGIRI
Services have come to a close.
His uniform hangs lifelessly
in the closet.
Alongside, his shoes, socks, shirts,
and pants recall
an elderly but youthful spirit,
unapologetic of his idiosyncrasies.
Eventually, his belongings
will likely be discarded
For, despite his daughter's
reluctance to part with
her cherished mementos,
his possessions will
never be worn again.
I'm sure Josuke needs
his privacy right now
Don't touch anything that's not
from a bottle or can.
We can't afford to take any risks.
Where'd your mom go?
I had her visit our relatives'
after the funeral.
Wise man.
She can return after
we knock the shit out of Angelo.
I'm not pissed, you know.
Just got a little worked up,
that's all.
Never been calmer, in fact.
Never been calmer, huh?
Well, it is your house.
Suppose you can take it out
on whatever please.
By the way,
that scratch on your lip…
I gave that to you
when I punched you, didn't I?
Can't your Stand heal
your own wounds?
No, my Stand can't heal
my own wounds.
What if his Stand infiltrates your body
and tries to eat his way out?
Then I guess I'm dead.
He gets me, I lose.
Think you can trap my
Stand in a bottle again, huh?
Well, think again.
I already know what you can do.
Tomorrow or the next day…
My moment'll come.
And I've got all the time in the world!
— 3 DAYS LATER —
He's sniffing around here
right under our noses…
But it's been three days,
and he still hasn't made a move.
What's he waiting for?
It's raining…
Rain?
What the hell?
I thought there was
something fishy about you.
So you're a Stand user, too, eh?
No matter.
My moment is finally here.
This house is mine!
You're not going anywhere
in this rain!
Josuke!
He must've just boiled the water.
He left all the faucets on, too.
I just saw Angelo's Stand
enter the house.
He wasn't waiting for you
to drink the water.
He was waiting for the rain!
His Stand can move anywhere
in the rain…
No…
It can move between
liquid and vapor!
Josuke! Get away from the kettle!
He morphed into the steam!
Just great.
We can't capture him
in the bottle.
Stay away from any steam.
Protect your lungs!
We need to get out of here.
Yeah, about that…
I'm not so sure there's
a whole lot we can do.
Angelo's already put a bunch
of holes in the roof.
Upstairs'll be no better,
and we'll be sitting ducks outside.
This is just great…
Gotta admit
this liquid-morphing Stand
is a lot freakier
than I anticipated.
He's a clever bastard.
What's so funny?
Son of a bitch's got us trapped!
Hey!
Well, Mr. Jotaro…
Grandpa's killer just about
handed himself in.
Pretty great, isn't it?!
Time to finish this.
So, Josuke…
What do you think?
How do we get out of this?
Get out?
I'm thinking more…
Home improvement!
Come on, this way!
The wall's gonna repair itself.
Good grief.
Well, we've blocked the steam…
The humidifier!
Josuke!
I win!
Just as I predicted, Josuke!
I thought you'd break through
the wall and come into this room!
Shit!
I guess it's like
winning at the races
or picking all the
right answers on a test…
When you guess right,
you can't help but giggle!
It just happens!
Josuke!
Angelo's got it all wrong,
Mr. Jotaro.
Josuke?
Whenever my prediction
proves true,
I don't feel like laughing…
Not when it comes to Angelo.
That's…
Got him.
It is kinda gross.
My apologies.
I cut up a rubber glove into
little pieces and swallowed it.
Slick.
Looks like
the user's over there.
Sh-Shit!
So you're…
…Angelo.
Son of a bitch!
You guys wouldn't kill me!
Sure, I escaped death row.
Sure, Japanese law
found me guilty.
But you guys have no
right to do anything to me!
Josuke!
I killed your grandpa,
but you can't put me to death!
If you kill me, you'll end up
cursed, like yours truly!
Didn't your mommy ever
teach you it's rude to point?
M-M-My hand! My hand!
No one's going to execute you.
Not me or Mr. Jotaro, here.
For you, there will be no execution,
and no incarceration.
Josuke, you handle the rest.
Wh-What the hell you
gonna do, you bastards?!
Enjoy your
eternal penance, Angelo!
Contemplate the life
you took from grandpa,
and everyone else you killed!
Here, you'll remain for all eternity,
in the town my grandfather
loved and protected.
Angelo's Rock.
MORIOH LANDMARK 1
ANGELO'S ROCK
ONE MINUTE WALK FROM
MORIOH JOZENJI STREET BUS STOP #3
Angelo's Rock: town landmark
and hot-spot for
romantic rendezvous.
For years it's charmed
the residents of Morioh,
despite its slightly
disturbing appearance.
This guy's bat shit crazy
Good grief..
EPISODE 3
THE NIJIMURA BROTHERS, PART 1